Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Soutenez Admin Watch sur kissasia.cam ou kisskh.org
[Blood River]
[Rivière de sang]
[Based on the novel of the same name from Zhou Munan's Youth in Jianghu series]
[Basé sur le roman du même nom de la série Jeunesse au Jianghu de Zhou Munan]
[Available on fanqienovel.com & bkneng.com]
[Disponible sur fanqienovel.com et bkneng.com]
[Episode 10]
[Épisode 10]
I disagree with much
Je suis en désaccord avec beaucoup de choses
of what Changhe said,
de ce que Changhe a dit,
but one thing
mais une chose
was no empty talk:
ce n'était pas un discours creux :
together, the two of us
ensemble, nous deux
have never lost.
n'ont jamais perdu.
Eighteen-Sword Array,
Tableau des dix-huit épées,
Activate!
Activer!
Great.
Super.
Excellent!
Excellent!
Eighteen-Sword Array?
Tableau de dix-huit épées ?
The greatest regret of my life
Le plus grand regret de ma vie
is
est
not being born a hundred years earlier
ne pas être né cent ans plus tôt
to face the Su family's finest,
pour affronter la crème de la famille Su,
Su Shiba, in battle.
Su Shiba, au combat.
Who would've thought that after I was sealed
Qui aurait pensé qu'après avoir été scellé
inside a coffin,
à l'intérieur d'un cercueil,
the Su family
la famille Su
would produce another who could revive the Eighteen-Sword Array?
produirait quelqu'un d'autre qui pourrait faire revivre la matrice des dix-huit épées ?
You're so talkative.
Tu es tellement bavard.
I've been trapped in that coffin
J'ai été piégé dans ce cercueil
for so many years,
pendant tant d'années,
of course, I have much to say
bien sûr, j'ai beaucoup à dire
and many fights yet to fight.
et encore beaucoup de combats à mener.
These swords of yours aren't enough to take me down.
Ces épées ne suffiront pas à me vaincre.
Show me
Montre-moi
your true strike.
votre véritable coup.
Then I'll grant your wish.
Alors j'exaucerai ton souhait.
Drizzle Sword.
Épée de bruine.
What's that?
Qu'est ce que c'est?
He's absorbing my sword energy.
Il absorbe l'énergie de mon épée.
So
Donc
this is what makes Hell Palm so terrifying.
c'est ce qui rend Hell Palm si terrifiant.
What a fool.
Quel idiot.
You've got some nerve to use your palm against me.
Tu as du culot d'utiliser ta paume contre moi.
Open your eyes wide
Ouvre grand les yeux
to see who the real fool is.
pour voir qui est le vrai fou.
Changhe.
Changement.
I didn't know
Je ne savais pas
that besides me,
qu'à part moi,
there was someone in the Blood River
il y avait quelqu'un dans la rivière de sang
bold enough
assez audacieux
to defy the rules.
défier les règles.
You've been secretly practicing the Hell Palm.
Vous avez pratiqué secrètement la Paume de l'Enfer.
Secretly?
Secrètement?
Judging from how things turned out,
À en juger par la tournure que prennent les événements,
I'd say I was just early to start.
Je dirais que j'étais juste trop tôt pour commencer.
What a shame.
Quelle honte.
If your cultivation in the Hell Palm
Si votre culture est dans le palmier de l'enfer
were one level higher,
étaient un niveau plus haut,
you could've beaten me.
tu aurais pu me battre.
But alas.
Mais hélas.
The Ten Courts of Hell
Les dix tribunaux de l'enfer
each rule over life and death.
chaque règle sur la vie et la mort.
You're
Tu es
one step short.
un pas de moins.
Darn it.
Zut alors.
How can a man who just crawled out of a coffin
Comment un homme qui vient de sortir d'un cercueil peut-il
have such profound inner force?
avez-vous une force intérieure si profonde ?
I looked pathetic.
J'avais l'air pathétique.
Changhe,
Changhe,
do you really mean to lead them
est-ce que tu veux vraiment les diriger ?
to the other shore?
vers l'autre rive ?
Of course,
Bien sûr,
even though this is only the beginning.
même si ce n'est que le début.
I've always been the only one
J'ai toujours été le seul
who prefers to stay away from strife.
qui préfère rester loin des conflits.
Since this is fate's will,
Puisque telle est la volonté du destin,
I'll sever it with my sword.
Je le couperai avec mon épée.
Hold the Dormant Dragon Sword
Tenez l'épée du dragon endormi
and become the first
et devenir le premier
Patriarch
Patriarche
as a Nameless.
comme un Sans Nom.
You finally came around.
Tu as finalement changé d'avis.
We were born
Nous sommes nés
to fight our fate.
pour combattre notre destin.
If you wish to wield the sword, then let's do it.
Si tu veux manier l'épée, alors faisons-le.
Only death
Seulement la mort
can stop us.
peut nous arrêter.
I'll find you an opening to wield that sword.
Je te trouverai une ouverture pour manier cette épée.
Such arrogance.
Quelle arrogance.
Yue'an,
Yue'an,
if you only have one chance to strike,
si vous n'avez qu'une seule chance de frapper,
close your eyes,
ferme les yeux,
and trust the judgment
et fais confiance au jugement
you're most certain of in that moment.
dont vous êtes le plus sûr à ce moment-là.
Su Muyu,
Su Muyu,
I can't hold on anymore!
Je ne peux plus tenir le coup !
I'm running out of strength.
Je suis à bout de force.
That slash
Cette barre oblique
damaged your heart meridian.
endommagé votre méridien cardiaque.
If you keep insisting,
Si vous continuez à insister,
you'll die.
tu vas mourir.
You two...
Vous deux...
What were your names again?
Comment vous appeliez-vous déjà ?
Su Muyu.
Su Muyu.
I'm Su Changhe.
Je m'appelle Su Changhe.
Very good.
Très bien.
Your names
Vos noms
will be known across the land.
sera connu dans tout le pays.
We'll meet again.
Nous nous reverrons.
Very good.
Très bien.
You two
Vous deux
are indeed impressive.
sont en effet impressionnants.
I'll look forward
J'attends avec impatience
to our next encounter.
à notre prochaine rencontre.
Su Muyu,
Su Muyu,
if you really want to quit,
si tu veux vraiment arrêter,
the promise we made before
la promesse que nous avons faite auparavant
doesn't stand anymore.
ne tient plus debout.
As for the powers behind all this that you mentioned,
Quant aux pouvoirs derrière tout ce que vous avez mentionné,
I'll root them out
Je vais les déraciner
in no time.
en un rien de temps.
Alright.
Bien.
That being said, the Hell Palm is too dangerous.
Cela étant dit, le Hell Palm est trop dangereux.
One slip,
Un glissement,
and it could backfire on you.
et cela pourrait se retourner contre vous.
You ought to be extra careful.
Vous devriez être très prudent.
It's not easy
Ce n'est pas facile
for us to have come this far.
pour que nous soyons arrivés jusqu'ici.
But
Mais
I'll keep moving forward.
Je continuerai d'avancer.
Changhe...
Changhe...
I know what you're going to say.
Je sais ce que tu vas dire.
I'll announce to the world,
J'annoncerai au monde,
from today on,
à partir d'aujourd'hui,
there'll be no more Umbrella Ghost in the Blood River.
il n'y aura plus de fantôme parapluie dans la rivière de sang.
I'll destroy the Soul Reapers' Hall,
Je détruirai la salle des faucheurs d'âmes,
so no one
donc personne
can ever issue another writ to kill you again.
ne pourra jamais émettre un autre mandat pour vous tuer à nouveau.
As well as the family
Tout comme la famille
you wish to take with you.
vous souhaitez emporter avec vous.
You once said you liked Nan'an.
Tu as dit un jour que tu aimais Nan'an.
I bought a mansion there
J'ai acheté un manoir là-bas
with the savings I stashed away over the years.
avec les économies que j'ai mises de côté au fil des années.
Go to Nan'an and find
Allez à Nan'an et trouvez
the owner of Shouyue Banking House.
le propriétaire de la Shouyue Banking House.
He'll give you the deed.
Il vous donnera l'acte.
There are ten thousand taels of silver
Il y a dix mille taels d'argent
buried under the courtyard.
enterré sous la cour.
If you run out of money,
Si vous manquez d’argent,
dig it up.
déterre-le.
Every autumn...
Chaque automne...
Every autumn,
Chaque automne,
when osmanthus fills Nan'an City,
quand l'osmanthus remplit la ville de Nan'an,
I'll come find you for a drink.
Je viendrai te chercher pour boire un verre.
Of course,
Bien sûr,
if you'd rather no one,
si tu préfères personne,
including me, know where you are,
moi y compris, sachez où vous êtes,
you can sell the mansion back
tu peux revendre le manoir
to the Shouyue Banking House.
à la Shouyue Banking House.
Still,
Toujours,
every autumn,
chaque automne,
when osmanthus fills Nan'an City,
quand l'osmanthus remplit la ville de Nan'an,
I'll hope to see you again.
J'espère te revoir.
Changhe.
Changement.
You never belonged here.
Tu n'as jamais appartenu à cet endroit.
Leaving this place is what you were meant to do.
Quitter cet endroit est ce que tu étais censé faire.
As for me,
Quant à moi,
I crawled out from piles of dead bodies when I was a child.
Quand j'étais enfant, je me suis extirpé d'une pile de cadavres.
To me, life
Pour moi, la vie
was never worth much.
n'a jamais valu grand chose.
If I leave,
Si je pars,
I wouldn't even know where to go.
Je ne saurais même pas où aller.
But you're a fool, really.
Mais tu es vraiment un imbécile.
You hate killing,
Tu détestes tuer,
yet it's the only thing you're good at.
et pourtant c'est la seule chose pour laquelle tu es bon.
You know nothing else.
Tu ne sais rien d'autre.
You've been the Kui for years,
Tu es le Kui depuis des années,
and you're still broke.
et tu es toujours fauché.
If you lived in the mortal world,
Si vous viviez dans le monde des mortels,
you'd definitely be cheated.
tu serais certainement trompé.
Farewell.
Adieu.
Su Muyu.
Su Muyu.
You call me a fool.
Tu m'appelles un imbécile.
You're just as much of a fool.
Tu es tout aussi idiot.
Remember we went to Luohe City
Je me souviens que nous sommes allés à la ville de Luohe
on our first mission
lors de notre première mission
to kill Li Huan, the one who embezzled relief funds?
tuer Li Huan, celui qui a détourné les fonds de secours ?
We could've finished him with one strike,
Nous aurions pu l'achever d'un seul coup,
but you insisted on tracing the clues
mais tu as insisté pour retrouver les indices
and took
et a pris
all his money and valuables.
tout son argent et ses objets de valeur.
And what happened?
Et que s'est-il passé ?
We were surrounded
Nous étions encerclés
by 32 constables from the Six Gates Bureau
par 32 agents du Six Gates Bureau
and nearly died in his mansion.
et a failli mourir dans son manoir.
That's because...
C'est parce que...
Shut up.
Fermez-la.
And that time
Et cette fois
at Xuehe Manor,
au manoir Xuehe,
when we went after the Sword Ghost, Wang Ba.
quand nous sommes partis à la poursuite du fantôme de l'épée, Wang Ba.
You just had to sneak into his library,
Il suffisait de se faufiler dans sa bibliothèque,
saying you wanted to collect some martial arts manuals,
disant que tu voulais récupérer des manuels d'arts martiaux,
and we ended up trapped by his mechanisms.
et nous avons fini par être piégés par ses mécanismes.
Luckily, I had
Heureusement, j'avais
some food on me,
un peu de nourriture sur moi,
and we managed to last three days and three nights
et nous avons réussi à tenir trois jours et trois nuits
before reinforcements arrived.
avant l'arrivée des renforts.
Otherwise, we would've starved to death.
Sinon, nous serions morts de faim.
We didn't die, did we?
Nous ne sommes pas morts, n'est-ce pas ?
And what happened at Lingnan,
Et ce qui s'est passé à Lingnan,
the East Sea,
la mer de l'Est,
and the Lei Fortress.
et la forteresse de Lei.
Every time, you turned
À chaque fois, tu te retournais
a simple task
une tâche simple
into a mess of trouble.
dans un pétrin de problèmes.
If you ever became the Patriarch,
Si jamais vous deveniez patriarche,
your greed and ambition
votre cupidité et votre ambition
would surge like the tide
monterait comme la marée
and drown everyone
et noyer tout le monde
who followed you.
qui t'a suivi.
You'd only become a madman
Tu deviendrais juste un fou
without restraint.
sans retenue.
So
Donc
I'll calm the storm with you.
Je calmerai la tempête avec toi.
The old promise still counts,
The old promise still counts,
but we'll switch our roles.
but we'll switch our roles.
Su Changhe,
Su Changhe,
once we get out of here,
once we get out of here,
you'll be the Patriarch,
you'll be the Patriarch,
and I'll lead the Su family.
and I'll lead the Su family.
I'll be with you.
I'll be with you.
We'll bring forth
We'll bring forth
a new Blood River.
a new Blood River.
All right.
All right.
Just like back at the Wailing Abyss.
Just like back at the Wailing Abyss.
Only that time,
Only that time,
it was you holding me up.
it was you holding me up.
♪Just one line...♪
???Just one line...???
Some debts
Some debts
always have to be repaid.
always have to be repaid.
♪Mountains and rivers meet and apart, it's you that I rely on...♪
???Mountains and rivers meet and apart, it's you that I rely on...???
To be honest,
To be honest,
till the very end,
till the very end,
I still didn't think you'd stay.
I still didn't think you'd stay.
♪This weary journey finds its end, only because♪
???This weary journey finds its end, only because???
♪I'm lucky to meet you♪
???I'm lucky to meet you???
Back then,
Back then,
Sikong Changfeng, third city lord of Xueyue City,
Sikong Changfeng, third city lord of Xueyue City,
shattered the Lone Void Array spanning a hundred li
shattered the Lone Void Array spanning a hundred li
with a single thrust of his spear.
with a single thrust of his spear.
I suppose
I suppose
his power must've been immeasurable.
his power must've been immeasurable.
But when I swung my sword,
But when I swung my sword,
I could only clear the space three chi before me.
I could only clear the space three chi before me.
This really is
This really is
a tough fight.
a tough fight.
Mu Zizhe got away.
Mu Zizhe got away.
The remaining disciples of the Mu
The remaining disciples of the Mu
and Xie families
and Xie families
have all surrendered.
have all surrendered.
What exactly is going on?
What exactly is going on?
The Three Families are history now.
The Three Families are history now.
The new Blood River
The new Blood River
is about to reach the other shore.
is about to reach the other shore.
Regroup with Su Changhe.
Regroup with Su Changhe.
Well, I'm old.
Well, I'm old.
When it comes to scheming against the human heart,
When it comes to scheming against the human heart,
Su Changhe really
Su Changhe really
leaves nothing to chance.
leaves nothing to chance.
You made a horrible decision,
You made a horrible decision,
Sir.
Sir.
I'm not the Patriarch anymore.
I'm not the Patriarch anymore.
I once bore the surname Mu
I once bore the surname Mu
and Su,
and Su,
yet I can never really leave this river.
yet I can never really leave this river.
Perhaps this upheaval
Perhaps this upheaval
could bring forth a new Blood River
could bring forth a new Blood River
and become
and become
a different shadow
a different shadow
in this world.
in this world.
Naive.
Naive.
A shadow
A shadow
is still a shadow.
is still a shadow.
It can never go somewhere bright.
It can never go somewhere bright.
Then I shall see for myself.
Then I shall see for myself.
But, Sir,
But, Sir,
whatever the outcome,
whatever the outcome,
you won't get to see it.
you won't get to see it.
I, Su Changhe, from the Su family,
I, Su Changhe, from the Su family,
have gained the current Patriarch's approval
have gained the current Patriarch's approval
and been granted the Dormant Dragon Sword.
and been granted the Dormant Dragon Sword.
From this day forward,
From this day forward,
I'll assume the position of Patriarch of the Blood River.
I'll assume the position of Patriarch of the Blood River.
Greetings to the new Patriarch,
Greetings to the new Patriarch,
Su Changhe.
Su Changhe.
Greetings, Sir.
Greetings, Sir.
The leader of Spider Shadow, Su Muyu,
The leader of Spider Shadow, Su Muyu,
will step down from the title of Kui.
will step down from the title of Kui.
He is now
He is now
the head of the Su family.
the head of the Su family.
Everyone,
Everyone,
the new Blood River
the new Blood River
has arrived.
has arrived.
Greetings, Sir.
Greetings, Sir.
Greetings, Master Su.
Greetings, Master Su.
Tang Lianyue.
Tang Lianyue.
[Yi's Residence]
[Yi's Residence]
[Yi Bu, Shadow Sect]
[Yi Bu, Shadow Sect]
Seems like
Seems like
[Xiao Yong, First Prince]
[Xiao Yong, First Prince]
this game
this game
is already lost.
is already lost.
That's too early to say.
That's too early to say.
Fair enough.
Fair enough.
Who knows,
Who knows,
there might be a divine move
there might be a divine move
that rose from despair.
that rose from despair.
Sir.
Sir.
[The Blood River's internal strife has ended. Mu Mingce and Xie Ba were killed.]
[The Blood River's internal strife has ended. Mu Mingce and Xie Ba were killed.]
[Su Jinhui and Mu Zizhe went missing.]
[Su Jinhui and Mu Zizhe went missing.]
[Su Changhe became the new Patriarch.]
[Su Changhe became the new Patriarch.]
[Su Muyu, Mu Qingyang, and Xie Qidao became the new family heads.]
[Su Muyu, Mu Qingyang, and Xie Qidao became the new family heads.]
It seems the one
It seems the one
who's truly playing against you
who's truly playing against you
has made his own
has made his own
divine move.
divine move.
These two young men
These two young men
actually...
actually...
Perhaps this is the best ending after all.
Perhaps this is the best ending after all.
Why
Why
is that so?
is that so?
Because they are strong.
Because they are strong.
Only a powerful rival
Only a powerful rival
can be
can be
the ally we now need.
the ally we now need.
[Nan'an City]
[Nan'an City]
[It's Grain Rain today.]
[It's Grain Rain today.]
[It marks the end of spring. The rain falls as affection grows deeper.]
[Cela marque la fin du printemps. La pluie tombe et l'affection s'approfondit.]
Hold it steady.
Tenez-le fermement.
Excuse me, miss.
Excusez-moi, mademoiselle.
I'd like one jin of osmanthus cake.
J'aimerais un jin de gâteau à l'osmanthus.
One jin...
Un jin...
One jin of osmanthus cake?
Un jin de gâteau à l'osmanthus ?
Yes, one jin of osmanthus cake.
Oui, un jin de gâteau à l'osmanthus.
All right.
D'accord.
Here's your osmanthus cake.
Voici votre gâteau à l'osmanthus.
Thank you.
Merci.
I'm back, Miss Bai.
Je suis de retour, Mademoiselle Bai.
I'm so tired.
Je suis si fatigué.
Later,
Plus tard,
when the medicine cools a little,
quand le médicament refroidit un peu,
drink it all.
bois tout.
Not a drop left.
Il n'en reste plus une goutte.
All right?
D'accord?
All right, Miss Bai.
Très bien, Mademoiselle Bai.
It's still hot.
Il fait encore chaud.
More patients have come today.
D'autres patients sont arrivés aujourd'hui.
It's the Grain Rain season.
C'est la saison des pluies de céréales.
The spring wind stirs the heart.
Le vent du printemps remue le cœur.
It's easy to fall ill.
Il est facile de tomber malade.
What kind of illness?
Quel genre de maladie ?
When the heart is stirred,
Quand le cœur est ému,
it's lovesickness.
c'est le mal d'amour.
The person you wanted to see is here.
La personne que vous vouliez voir est ici.
And the osmanthus cake I wanted to eat,
Et le gâteau à l'osmanthus que je voulais manger,
I got it.
J'ai compris.
Let's begin
Commençons
the consultations.
les consultations.
It starts now.
Ça commence maintenant.
Coming.
À venir.
What seems to be the problem?
Quel semble être le problème ?
Your hand.
Ta main.
What's your ailment?
Quel est ton problème de santé ?
Isn't that why I came
N'est-ce pas pour ça que je suis venu ?
to find out what ailment it is?
pour savoir de quelle maladie il s'agit ?
Ten taels of silver.
Dix taëls d'argent.
I'll have him
Je l'aurai
prepare your concoction.
préparez votre concoction.
What concoction?
Quelle concoction ?
[One tael of woad root]
[Un tael de racine de pastel]
Ten taels of silver.
Dix taëls d'argent.
Ten taels of silver
Dix taels d'argent
for one tael of woad root?
pour un tael de racine de pastel ?
If you don't want it,
Si tu n'en veux pas,
I'll give it to someone else.
Je le donnerai à quelqu'un d'autre.
I'll take it. I will.
Je le prendrai. Je le ferai.
Next, please.
Suivant, s'il vous plaît.
Why are there still so many in line?
Pourquoi y a-t-il encore autant de monde dans la file d'attente ?
Tell me about it.
Parlez-moi de ça.
Which number is she?
Quel est son numéro ?
I'll pay a hundred taels.
Je paierai cent taels.
I want him to feed me the medicine.
Je veux qu'il me donne le médicament.
[One hundred taels] One hundred taels?
[Cent taels] Cent taels ?
One hundred taels isn't enough.
Cent taels ne suffisent pas.
Two hundred taels.
Deux cents taels.
Deal.
Accord.
[A hundred taels]
[Cent taels]
Next, please.
Suivant, s'il vous plaît.
Stop staring.
Arrête de regarder.
Your condition is serious.
Votre état est grave.
Look at me
Regardez-moi
and listen carefully.
et écoutez attentivement.
Otherwise,
Sinon,
you won't make it through this spring.
tu ne survivras pas à ce printemps.
[Yi's Residence]
[Résidence de Yi]
After Su Muyu succeeded
Après le succès de Su Muyu
as head of the Su family,
en tant que chef de la famille Su,
he opened an apothecary in Nan'an City?
il a ouvert une apothicairerie dans la ville de Nan'an ?
Yes.
Oui.
We sent people to keep watch,
Nous avons envoyé des gens pour surveiller,
but they were discovered.
mais ils ont été découverts.
Someone intervened
Quelqu'un est intervenu
and crippled their martial skills.
et a paralysé leurs capacités martiales.
It seems to be a warning.
Cela semble être un avertissement.
We've only posted
Nous avons seulement posté
a few watchers
quelques observateurs
outside Nan'an City now.
à l'extérieur de la ville de Nan'an maintenant.
We have no idea
Nous n'en avons aucune idée
what they're up to.
ce qu'ils font.
What about Su Changhe?
Qu'en est-il de Su Changhe ?
He returned to Blood River.
Il est retourné à Blood River.
Judging by his moves,
À en juger par ses mouvements,
he's after the Soul Reapers' Hall.
il est après le Hall des Soul Reapers.
But the Three Officials have left.
Mais les trois fonctionnaires sont partis.
He took in the disciples from the Three Families who remained in Blood River,
Il accueillit les disciples des Trois Familles restés à Blood River,
and then left.
et puis c'est parti.
Send a message to the Three Officials.
Envoyez un message aux trois officiels.
Now is the time
C'est le moment
they meet.
ils se rencontrent.
Sir,
Monsieur,
is this to form an alliance with them?
Est-ce pour former une alliance avec eux ?
Even though an unruly sword
Même si une épée indisciplinée
is hard to control,
est difficile à contrôler,
if we hold it in our hands,
si nous le tenons dans nos mains,
only then can we achieve true domination.
Ce n’est qu’à ce moment-là que nous pourrons parvenir à une véritable domination.
Your Eighteen-Sword Array
Votre tableau de dix-huit épées
is amazing.
c'est incroyable.
I could sense your sword aura
Je pouvais sentir l'aura de ton épée
from a distance.
à distance.
But how will you retrieve
Mais comment vas-tu récupérer
the swords you release?
les épées que tu lâches ?
Changhe had the Ban family
Changhe avait la famille Ban
specially make this umbrella
fabriquer spécialement ce parapluie
for me.
pour moi.
Back then, when I launched the Eighteen-Sword Array,
À l’époque, lorsque j’ai lancé le réseau des dix-huit épées,
I used ordinary paper umbrellas.
J'ai utilisé des parapluies en papier ordinaires.
They broke easily,
Ils se sont cassés facilement,
and after each launch,
et après chaque lancement,
I had to gather the swords myself.
J'ai dû rassembler les épées moi-même.
Honestly,
Honnêtement,
if you ever have to use
si jamais vous devez utiliser
this sword array to attack in the future,
cette panoplie d'épées pour attaquer dans le futur,
wouldn't you have to
ne devrais-tu pas
pull the swords
tirer les épées
out of each body?
hors de chaque corps ?
There's no assassin in the world who would do that.
Il n’y a aucun assassin au monde qui ferait ça.
As long as the mission is completed.
Tant que la mission est accomplie.
They're dead,
Ils sont morts,
they won't see me gathering the swords.
ils ne me verront pas rassembler les épées.
I'll take more jobs
Je prendrai plus de travail
and save up
et économisez
to buy you a decent umbrella.
pour t'acheter un parapluie décent.
Otherwise, partnering with you
Sinon, en partenariat avec vous
on a killing mission
en mission meurtrière
would be too embarrassing.
Ce serait trop embarrassant.
Here.
Ici.
All right.
D'accord.
Thank you.
Merci.
You're so kind.
Tu es si gentil.
Changhe said
Changhe a déclaré
an assassin shouldn't look like that
un assassin ne devrait pas ressembler à ça
after a kill.
après un meurtre.
This is just a sword.
Ce n'est qu'une épée.
Why must one possess it
Pourquoi faut-il le posséder ?
to rule Blood River?
pour gouverner Blood River ?
♪Like fate, winding with the tide♪
???Comme le destin, emporté par la marée???
♪Who can ford this river of night?♪
???Qui peut traverser à gué cette rivière de nuit ???
♪Where's the far shore we chase all our lives?♪
???Où est l'autre rive que nous poursuivons toute notre vie????
♪Surrendering all hues for a glimmer of light♪
???Abandonner toutes les teintes pour une lueur de lumière???
♪Through joy and sorrow♪
???À travers la joie et la tristesse???
♪Still I can't let go♪
???Je n'arrive toujours pas à lâcher prise???
♪Longing keeps me awake at night♪
???Le désir me tient éveillé la nuit???
♪My heart no longer my own♪
???Mon cœur ne m'appartient plus???
♪No one can escape from love♪
???Personne ne peut échapper à l'amour???
♪How many hidden feelings♪
???Combien de sentiments cachés???
♪Sink in silence deep?♪
???S'enfoncer dans le silence profond????
♪Searching through the endless nights♪
???À la recherche des nuits sans fin???
♪Struggling on the edge of love and pain♪
???Lutter à la frontière de l'amour et de la douleur???
♪Shadows crossing shadows♪
???Des ombres traversant des ombres???
♪Whose name hides in your eyes?♪
???Quel nom se cache dans tes yeux????
♪When the wind blows, ask not when I shall return♪
???Quand le vent souffle, ne demande pas quand je reviendrai???
♪Ask not when I shall return♪
???Ne demandez pas quand je reviendrai???
♪Like fate, winding with the tide♪
???Comme le destin, emporté par la marée???
♪Who can ford this river of night?♪
???Qui peut traverser à gué cette rivière de nuit ???
♪Where's the far shore we chase all our lives?♪
???Où est l'autre rive que nous poursuivons toute notre vie????
♪Surrendering all hues for a glimmer of light♪
???Abandonner toutes les teintes pour une lueur de lumière???
♪Through joy and sorrow♪
???À travers la joie et la tristesse???
♪Still I can't let go♪
???Je n'arrive toujours pas à lâcher prise???
♪Longing keeps me awake at night♪
???Le désir me tient éveillé la nuit???
♪My heart no longer my own♪
???Mon cœur ne m'appartient plus???
♪No one can escape from love♪
???Personne ne peut échapper à l'amour???